expertsforge.com 2007-12-11

# Expertsforge.com - Privacy Policy

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This policy covers how Expertsforge treats personal information that Expertsforge collects during time of registration. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.   

  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Expertsforge does not own or control, or to people that Expertsforge does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

**General**

  * Expertsforge collects personal information when you register with Expertsforge, when you use Expertsforge products or services, when you visit Expertsforge pages or the pages of certain Expertsforge partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes.   

  * Expertsforge may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.  

  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry.   

  * Expertsforge automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address.   

  * Expertsforge uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**Children**

  * We do not encourage child under age 13 attempts to register with Expertsforge and it is mentioned in Rules.  

  * If a child under 13 needs to register with Expertsforge it should be done only under the parental Guidance.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * Expertsforge does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:  

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Expertsforge under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Expertsforge communicate with you about offers from Expertsforge and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.  

  * We transfer information about you if Expertsforge is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Expertsforge will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  

  * Expertsforge does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

**Confidentiality and Security**

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * Expertsforge may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Expertsforge account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a feedback form or you can contact us here or

**Expertsforge.com**  
25 B, KKS Street,BR Puram,  
Peelamedu,  
Coimbatore - 641004  
Tamil Nadu.  
India
